[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word berserk referring to Norse warriors, means what in Old Norse?", "correct_answer": "Bear Shirt", "incorrect_answers": ["Warriors Wrath", "Warriors Rage", "Beer Shirt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The national motto of this Arabic country is God is the greatest.", "correct_answer": "Iraq", "incorrect_answers": ["Morocco", "Iran", "Syria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Referring to the previous question, if its 6:00 P.M. in Ossining, NY, what time is it in Honolulu, Hawaii?", "correct_answer": "12 Noon", "incorrect_answers": ["3:00 PM", "12 Midnight", "Time to surf, Brah!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During a Vivienne Westwood catwalk show in 1993, which supermodel fell because she was wearing extremely high blue shoes?", "correct_answer": "Naomi Campbell", "incorrect_answers": ["Vanessa Paradis", "Heidi Klum", "Kate Moss"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "We all know that when arrested you must be Mirandized. Of what crime or crimes was Mr. Miranda accused?", "correct_answer": "Rape and kidnapping", "incorrect_answers": ["Murder", "Murder and rape", "Grand theft"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Calores Montes?", "correct_answer": "a range of mountains on Mercury", "incorrect_answers": ["a large crater on Mercury", "a tall mountain on Mercury", "a volcano on Mercury"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which game show was hit by a scandal in 1958?", "correct_answer": "Twenty-One", "incorrect_answers": ["Jeopardy", "The $64,000 Challenge", "The $64,000 Question"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Throughout the period from the 1970s to the end of the 20th century, the rhinoceros numbers declined by approximately what percentage?", "correct_answer": "90%", "incorrect_answers": ["50%", "60%", "75%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vampire bats have poor eyesight.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Lord of the Rings, which of these is a son of Denethor II, the twenty-sixth and last Ruling Steward of Gondor?", "correct_answer": "Faramir", "incorrect_answers": ["Aragorn", "Baramir", "Theoden"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1966 movie Batman, based on the ABC TV series, all but one of the villains listed were played by the TV series actors/actresses. Which character was not played by one of the original actors?", "correct_answer": "Catwoman", "incorrect_answers": ["Penguin", "Riddler", "Joker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During Roman occupation, this city, popular nowadays as the Heaven of Romance, was called Lutetia.", "correct_answer": "Paris", "incorrect_answers": ["Venice", "London", "Rome"]}]